Subtitle Provide by dramacool.asia Translator [Admin.@YNG]
تم توفير الترجمة بواسطة مترجم dramacool.asia [Admin.@YNG]
=Twin Fates=
=مصيران توأمان=
=Episode 11= (Birthday Celebrations)
=الحلقة 11= (احتفالات عيد الميلاد)
My skills are not yet refined.
مهاراتي لم تتطور بعد.
Please forgive me, Your Majesty.
أرجوك أن تسامحني يا جلالتك.
Iron trees bloom with silver flowers.
تزهر الأشجار الحديدية بأزهار فضية.
A thousand stars light up the sky.
ألف نجمة تضيء السماء.
Your craft has won my heart.
لقد فازت حرفتك بقلبي.
Huh? What's the matter, Chi Yu?
هاه؟ ما الأمر يا تشي يو؟
Chi Yu?
تشي يو؟
What's gotten into you, Chi Yu?
ما الذي حدث لك يا تشي يو؟
You really put on a grand show.
لقد قدمت عرضًا رائعًا حقًا.
Facing your enemy,
في مواجهة عدوك،
you spare their life
أنت تنقذ حياتهم
and instead put on a show of charm.
وبدلاً من ذلك، أظهروا مظهرًا من السحر.
Chi Yu, I wish you health and happiness
تشي يو، أتمنى لك الصحة والسعادة
on this Lantern Festival and your birthday.
في مهرجان الفوانيس هذا وفي عيد ميلادك.
Congratulations to you, Scarlet Flame Lord of War,
مبروك لك يا سيد الحرب القرمزي اللهب،
on a joyous Lantern Festival and birthday.
في مهرجان الفوانيس السعيد وعيد الميلاد.
I've heard the Scarlet Flame lands
لقد سمعت أن اللهب القرمزي يهبط
once bloomed with iron fireworks.
كانت تزدهر ذات يوم بالألعاب النارية الحديدية.
Though I never saw it myself,
رغم أنني لم أره بنفسي قط،
that performance was the closest
كان هذا الأداء هو الأقرب
I could imagine.
أستطيع أن أتخيل.
Do you like this birthday gift?
هل تعجبك هدية عيد الميلاد هذه؟
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
You're not upset anymore?
هل أنت لست منزعجا بعد الآن؟
I still can't stand to see you
لا أزال لا أستطيع أن أتحمل رؤيتك
flattering and bending
مُتملق ومُنحني
to your enemies.
إلى أعدائك.
Ji Yuchen can't die yet.
جي يوشين لا يمكن أن يموت بعد.
He sentenced your whole family to death.
لقد حكم على عائلتك بأكملها بالإعدام.
My father was falsely accused of treason.
لقد اتُهم والدي زوراً بالخيانة.
Why should I prove his guilt
لماذا يجب أن أثبت ذنبه؟
by killing the emperor?
بقتل الإمبراطور؟
I want justice and vengeance for spilled blood,
أريد العدالة والانتقام للدماء المسفوكة،
but more than that, I want justice to be restored.
ولكن أكثر من ذلك، أريد استعادة العدالة.
Why do you think he would clear your name?
لماذا تعتقد أنه سوف يبرئ اسمك؟
I'm powerless
أنا عاجز
and insignificant.
وغير مهمة.
Without trust or help,
بدون ثقة أو مساعدة،
how can I clear the Mu Residence's name?
كيف يمكنني مسح اسم Mu Residence؟
That's why I have to get close to Ji Yuchen,
لهذا السبب يجب أن أكون قريبًا من جي يوتشن،
use his power
استخدم قوته
to uncover the truth
لكشف الحقيقة
and expose the real culprit
وكشف الجاني الحقيقي
behind the Mu family's tragedy.
وراء مأساة عائلة مو.
Do you trust me?
هل تثق بي؟
I do.
أفعل.
Peace and reunion to all
السلام والالتقاء للجميع
on the Lantern Festival.
في مهرجان الفوانيس.
I haven't had
لم يكن لدي
the wheat cakes this year.
كعك القمح هذا العام.
My mother used to make the best.
كانت والدتي تصنع الأفضل.
I'll never taste them again.
لن أتذوقهم مرة أخرى.
(Lord Yi's Residence)
(مقر إقامة اللورد يي)
Chi Yu.
تشي يو.
For you.
لك.
What's this?
ما هذا؟
These are wheat cakes.
هذه هي كعكات القمح.
Leave the items and go.
اترك العناصر واذهب.
Thank you, sir! Thank you!
شكراً لك سيدي! شكراً لك!
Is this
هذا هو
a phoenix?
طائر الفينيق؟
Yes.
نعم.
Wait, Chi Yu!
انتظر، تشي يو!
Chi Yu! Chi Yu.
تشي يو! تشي يو.
Chi Yu. Chi Yu!
تشي يو. تشي يو!
You can't take back a gift.
لا يمكنك استعادة الهدية.
I'll eat it.
سوف آكله.
Give it to me.
أعطيني إياه.
Give it to me!
أعطيني إياه!
Chi Yu, I want to eat it.
تشي يو أريد أن آكله.
Chi Yu,
تشي يو,
come on. Give it to me.
تعال. أعطني إياه.
(Lord Yi's Residence)
(مقر إقامة اللورد يي)
Foreign envoys brought a batch
وقد أحضر المبعوثون الأجانب دفعة
of exquisite thousand-layer silk as a tribute for the Lantern Festival.
من الحرير الفاخر المكون من ألف طبقة تكريمًا لمهرجان الفوانيس.
His Majesty specifically ordered us
لقد أمرنا جلالته على وجه التحديد
to tailor garments for Your Highness.
لتفصيل الملابس لسموك.
Your Highness is very sensitive.
سموكم حساس للغاية.
I believe it's time
أعتقد أن الوقت قد حان
to take your waist measurements?
لأخذ قياسات خصرك؟
Yes.
نعم.
Her waist measures one chi and eight cun.
يبلغ قياس خصرها تشي واحد وثمانية كون.
Her shoulders span two palms.
كتفيها تمتد على مدى راحتي يديها.
Feng has a keen eye.
لدى فينج عين ثاقبة.
I'm ticklish, so I don't like being touched.
أنا دغدغة، لذلك أنا لا أحب أن يتم لمسي.
He's been reporting my measurements for years for me.
لقد كان يقدم لي قياساتي لسنوات عديدة.
If there is any falseness,
إذا كان هناك أي زيف،
you will be guilty of deceiving me.
سوف تكون مذنبا بخداعي.
Her bust measures two chi and eight cun.
يبلغ قياس تمثال نصفي لها اثنين تشي وثمانية كون.
Anything else you need to know?
هل هناك أي شيء آخر تحتاج إلى معرفته؟
Brother, I used to roam alone in dangerous places.
أخي، كنت أتجول بمفردي في الأماكن الخطرة.
Feng's actions were unintentional.
كانت تصرفات فنغ غير مقصودة.
Please don't mind him.
من فضلك لا تهتم به.
I need to check the files in the archives.
أحتاج إلى التحقق من الملفات الموجودة في الأرشيف.
Let's call it a day.
فلنسميها يوما.
Why do you insist on provoking Ji Yuchen?
لماذا تصر على استفزاز جي يوتشن؟
I need his help
انا بحاجة لمساعدته
to reopen the Mu Residence case.
لإعادة فتح قضية مو ريزيدنس.
It's just to check a file.
إنه فقط للتحقق من الملف.
I could help you myself.
أستطيع مساعدتك بنفسي.
Why must you get Ji Yuchen's permission?
لماذا يجب عليك الحصول على إذن جي يوتشن؟
Are you jealous?
هل انت غيور؟
I don't have
ليس عندي
such silly human emotions.
هذه المشاعر الإنسانية السخيفة.
=Twin Fates= =End of Episode 11=
=مصيران توأمان= =نهاية الحلقة 11=
♪In a world of sorrows, every encounter is fleeting♪
♪في عالم من الأحزان، كل لقاء عابر♪
♪Life is short but slumber is long on Penglai Island♪
♪الحياة قصيرة ولكن النوم طويل في جزيرة بنغلاي♪
♪In dreams, mountains and flowers are as beautiful as jade♪
♪في الأحلام، الجبال والزهور جميلة مثل اليشم♪
♪All I ever wish for is an old friend's return♪
♪كل ما أتمناه هو عودة صديق قديم♪
♪Majestic as a soaring dragon, veiling the sun with drifting clouds♪
♪مهيب مثل التنين المرتفع، يحجب الشمس بالغيوم المنجرفة♪
♪Graceful as a flying swan goose, breaking through snow and peril♪
♪رشيقة مثل أوزة البجعة الطائرة، تخترق الثلوج والخطر♪
♪Twenty years forsaken, I lived the life of an outlaw♪
♪بعد عشرين عامًا من الإهمال، عشت حياة خارج عن القانون♪
♪On the Ximo River, who was left behind?♪
♪على نهر شيمو، من بقي خلفه؟♪
♪Bit by bit, reality shatters my only hope♪
♪شيئًا فشيئًا، الواقع يحطم أملي الوحيد♪
♪Layer by layer, cold blades roll up the light I once glimpsed in secret♪
♪طبقة بعد طبقة، شفرات باردة تتدحرج نحو الضوء الذي لمحته ذات مرة سرًا♪
♪Letters have long since yellowed♪
♪لقد اصفرت الحروف منذ زمن طويل♪
♪Leaving only two lonely lines♪
♪ترك خطين وحيدين فقط♪
♪Even the old yard is covered with frost♪
♪حتى الفناء القديم مغطى بالصقيع♪
♪Pair after pair, swallows draw my envious gaze♪
♪زوجًا بعد زوج، تجذب السنونو نظرتي الحسود♪
♪Scene after scene, in dreams I cannot reach♪
♪مشهد بعد مشهد، في الأحلام لا أستطيع الوصول إليه♪
♪While you rest beneath the earth♪
♪بينما تستريح تحت الأرض♪
♪My love lingers in this frosty world♪
♪حبي يبقى في هذا العالم البارد♪
♪How are you now?♪
♪كيف حالك الآن؟♪